本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
翻譯：毒舌萌妹YY貓  蟒蛇猛漢賽太公   阿蘅阿蘅
校對：毒舌萌妹YY貓  蟒蛇猛漢賽太公  總監 YY貓
壓制/特效：灰灰是菇涼   時間軸：YY貓
生
活
大
爆
炸
第八季  第十集
大家好
Hello.
我是謝爾頓·庫珀博士
I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
歡迎收看由謝爾頓·庫珀出品的《有趣的旗幟》
And welcome to Sheldon Cooper Presents: Fun with Flags,
最終集  壯麗的旗幟
the Final Episode Flagtacular.
我知道會有拉炮  還是嚇死人家了
I knew it was coming. Still scary.
我知道你們一定在想"居然最終集了
Now, I'm sure you're thinking, "The final episode?
是誰要害你們變成旗幟盲了"
who will stand between us and flag ignorance"
像我就有這個想法
I know I was thinking that.
這是旗幟節目還是讀心節目啊
Is this a show on flags or mind reading?
但事實上是因為我無法繼續兼顧全職工作
But the truth is I can no longer balance a full-time career,
熱門網絡節目  以及女朋友了
a popular Internet show, and a girlfriend.
他是真的有女朋友  你們這些留言的混球們
And he really does have one, you jerks on the comment board.
常言道  天下無不散之筵席
So as they say, all good things must come to an end.
雖然僅有232集視覺饗宴
After only 232 episodes.
如果某人有次
233 if we include the one
沒忘了按下錄制鍵  那應該是233集
somebody forgot to press record on.
說好了不提那事兒
You said you weren't gonna bring that up.
說好了你會按錄制鍵
And you said you pressed record.
總之  用放松的姿勢
Anyway, please sit back, relax,
跟著我們一起跑完這最后一圈
and join us as we take our final lap...
就像這只賽車旗指示的一樣
...as indicated by the waving of this racing flag.
白旗在不同系列車賽中有不同意義
有些代表場上有慢速車輛  有些則是最后一圈
當然  白旗也代表"舉白旗投降"
And, of course, white flags can also represent surrender,
剛鐸宰相  日本源氏也都使用白旗
the Stewards of Gondor, and the Japanese Minamoto clan,
剛鐸宰相  《魔戒》中剛鐸地區的統治者
日本源氏與平家大戰時  一家白旗  一家紅旗
但想必你們肯定還記得這些
but I'm sure you remember that from episode 62,
因為62集"白旗  誰舉白旗及緣由"都講過
"White Flags: Who's Wavin' 'Em and Why""
那集超贊
That was a good one.
的確是贊到爆炸
It was so good.
我本來以為清理過世教授的
You know, I thought cleaning out a dead professor's office
辦公室會很無聊
was gonna just be boring,
不過在我發現他的假牙后
but then I found his dentures
我才意識到是無聊加惡心
and realized it's also gross.
艾伯特教授的家人不想要這些東西嗎
Doesn't Professor Abbott's family want any of this stuff?
我記得他好像沒家人
I don't think he had a family.
-真慘  -是啊
- That's rough. - I know.
一生都奉獻給了工作
You can spend your whole life working,
最后留下的只有盒子里的一些研究資料
and at the end all that's left are some papers in a box.
不禁讓你思索人生
Makes you think.
算了吧
Oh, well.
我們都得仔細檢查過這些東西
Hey. Hey, we're supposed to look through all this stuff
以確保不會扔掉什么重要資料
before we throw it away in case it's important.
看啦  不是太舊就是被拒[反證]的
I-I did. It's all outdated or disproved.
不一定哦  這支舊筆"證明"了重力存在
I don't know. This old pen kind of proves gravity.
翻轉過來  小人偶的泳衣就掉下來
When I tilt it, her bathing suit falls right off.
我爸以前也有一支這樣的筆
Oh, my dad used to have a pen like that.
我整個六年級都跟它"約"會
I dated it all through sixth grade.
還是感覺很奇怪
It still feels weird
就這樣把這些研究成果都扔掉
just throwing away his work like this.
不用難過
Don't feel bad.
未來某天  也會有人來扔你的研究報告
Someday, someone will be throwing out your work, too.
那個人就是謝爾頓  而那個某天是昨天
That someone was Sheldon, and the day was yesterday.
你們瞧
Hey, look at this.
"親愛的羅杰  在你獲得首次重大發現時開
"Dear Roger, to be opened upon your first great discovery.
愛你  媽"
Love, Mom."
瞧瞧這日期
Wow, look at the date.
他留了整整50年  卻從沒有機會開
He saved this 50 years and never got to open it.
真是讓人惋惜
That's intense.
可憐的羅杰·艾伯特
Poor Roger Abbott.
羅杰特聽起來像羅杰兔
Roger Abbott sounds just like Roger Rabbit.
兔子羅杰是小說與電影的一個卡通人物
羅杰特  羅杰特  羅杰兔
Roger Abbott, Roger Abbott, Roger Rabbit.
天啊  萊納德  我知道這對死者不敬
Oh, my God, Leonard, I know he's dead,
不過你念念看  超好笑啊
but try it. It's fun!
羅杰特  羅杰特  羅杰兔
Roger Abbott, Roger Rabbit...
佩妮
Penny!
我的年度最佳新人
Oh, my rookie of the year.
丹  我一開始不想雇我
Oh, Dan. My boss who didn't want to hire me
但現在超愛抱我的老板
and now's a little hug machine.
看看你  新加入不久就業績第三名
Oh, look at you. Brand-new and already the third best sales rep.
-過來我那桌坐坐吧  -我馬上過去
- Why don't you come over to my table. - Yes. I'll be right there.
伯納黛特還在停車
Bernadette's just parking the car.
太好了
Oh, good.
伯納黛特  人萌音甜
Bernadette. Cute, sweet...
惡毒兇殘的小伯納黛特
vicious little Bernadette.
別這樣嘛  她沒那么壞
Come on. She's not that bad.
是嗎
Oh, yeah?
公司野餐的時候  她吼了我跟我孫子
At the company picnic she yelled at me and my grandson
因為我們輸了二人三腿賽跑
for losing the three-legged race.
我孫子現在還叫她為"毒舌大奶娃"
I mean, he still calls her "That mean kid with the big boobies."
她有時候是有點兇  但我保證
I know she can be a little intense, but, I swear,
等稍微熟了之后   她就是很親切的一個人了
she is so sweet once you get past all the...
你們在聊什么
Hey, what are you talking about?
我們在聊有多喜歡跟你共事
We were just talking about how much we love working with you.
對吧
Isn't that right?
丹
Dan?
在《有趣的旗幟》的這些歲月里
Over the years here at Fun With Flags,
我們有機會一同學習  歡笑  驚奇
we've had an opportunity to learn, laugh, wonder...
甚至落過幾滴淚
And, yes, even shed a tear or two.
比如國慶節做了兩小時特別節目
Like when you do a two-hour Fourth of July spectacular
結果卻沒被錄下來
and it doesn't get recorded.
到底要我道歉幾次才夠
How many times do I have to say I'm sorry?
先來個四千次吧
How about 4,000.
向我拼成美國國旗的每一片骨牌道歉
One for every domino I set up to make that American flag.
請欣賞我們的精彩剪輯
Please enjoy these highlights.
"澳"喲媽呀  今天是講哪國的旗呢
Crikey! What flag do we have today?
澳大利亞  兄弟[澳洲口音]
Australia, mate!
現在到了高速國旗大鑒定的單元
And now it's time for the speed round of Flag or Not a Flag.
國旗  國旗
Flag. Flag.
不是國旗  國旗
Not a flag. Flag.
我太厲害了
I am crushing this.
貝特西·羅斯  你在縫什么呢
Say, Betsy Ross, what you working on?
被美國公眾廣泛認作美國國旗的首位縫制者
但缺乏足夠的檔案記載以佐證這一觀點
我也不知道
I have no idea.
因為我縫出第一面美國旗幟的故事
Because the story of me sewing the first American flag
是沒證據的狗屁
is unsupported poppycock.
那到底是誰縫的呢
Then who did sew it, hmm?
別問我
Don't ask me.
我只是個普通的女裁縫  是我的后代
I'm just a simple seamstress whose descendants are...
想出來坑蒙拐騙
out to make a quick buck!
賞臉共泳嗎
Fancy a dip, my dear?
樂意之至
I do.
等等  紫色旗子代表了
Wait, that purple flag indicates
水域有海洋有害生物  比如毒水母
that marine pests, such as jellyfish, are present.
哇  這旗子拯"救生"命啊
Wow, that flag is a lifesaver.
不是
No.
這才是"救生"圈
This is.
別盯著人家腿了
Stop looking at my legs.
不是國旗  國旗
Not a flag. Flag.
國旗  不是國旗
Flag. Not a flag.
是的
Flag.
靠
Crap.
碰到這種讓我難受的事
When stuff like this gets me down,
你知道我都怎么做嗎
you know what I like to do?
像八歲小女孩一樣唱"哈庫那馬他他"嗎
Sing "Hakuna Matata" Like an eight-year-old girl?
《獅子王》電影中的歡樂歌曲
意為"不用擔心"或"沒有問題"
錯了  自作聰明
Wrong, smarty-pants.
是《樂高大電影》里的"啥事兒都好贊"
It's "Everything Is Awesome" From The Lego Movie.
該電影中的洗腦歡樂主題曲
看這些筆記本
Look at these notebooks.
一頁一頁全都是數據
They're full of pages and pages of data.
明顯是他多年的心血
He clearly spent years on this.
只是一行行無規律的數字  扔了吧
Oh, it's just columns of random numbers. Toss it.
萬一這是他可能的重要突破呢
Well, but what if this was a potential breakthrough for him?
萬一這是讓能他
What if... what if this is the thing
如愿以償打開那瓶香檳的東西呢
that would've finally let him open that bottle of champagne?
或許他不開  是因為不知道香檳要配什么
Maybe he didn't know what to pair champagne with.
草莓  魚子醬  生蠔  都是好選擇
Strawberries, caviar, oysters. All good choices.
瞧你那態度
Yeah, that look right there
所以大家才會在參加你派對前先吃飽
is why people eat before they come to your parties.
這些數據絕對是有意義的
This has to mean something.
我沒能看出有什么規律啊
Well, there's no discernible pattern that I can see,
不過輸進電腦里驗證應該是沒什么難度
but it shouldn't be too hard to run the numbers and check.
或許我們可以用超級計算機試試
Well, maybe we can get some time on the supercomputer.
可以啊  我們試試用不同的物理常數
Sure. We could try multiple regressions
與實驗常數進行多元回歸分析
with varying physical and experimental constants.
還可以用模式匹配算法
Oh, we could run a pattern-matching algorithm
將它們與知名未解物理問題做對比
against well-known unsolved physics problems.
甚至有可能是替換式密碼
Ooh, it might be a substitution cipher.
我們可以從基本密碼分析著手
We could start with basic cryptanalysis.
或者我們可以問以前跟他同一辦公室的人
Or we could talk to this guy he used to share an office with.
還是那樣做吧
Oh, let's do that.
因為你不知道怎么做密碼分析  對吧
Because you don't know how to do cryptanalysis, do you?
我甚至不確定我說的詞對不對
I'm not even sure if it's the right word.
丹  你有個孫子
So, Dan, you have a grandson.
-他幾歲了  -七歲
- How old is he? - Seven.
我記得他  在那次野餐有見過
Oh, yeah. I remember him from the picnic.
一直哭個不停  像個娘娘腔似地
He was the one crying like a wuss the whole time.
我聽說他是被一個小惡霸欺負了
I heard he was being picked on by a mean kid.
有助人格發展啊
Just builds character.
就像我爸說的  "沒人喜歡愛哭鬼
Like my dad said, "Nobody likes a crybaby
除了他們自己的媽還有民主黨"
except their mommies and Democrats."
失陪  我去加酒
I need another drink.
他是有啥不滿
What's his problem?
不知道  可能他不喜歡聽到
I don't know. Maybe he didn't like the fact
自己的孫子被你叫娘娘腔吧
that you called his grandson a wuss.
可現在不是不讓叫別人"娘炮"嗎
Well, I didn't think you were supposed to say "sissy" anymore.
我知道你這個人很好
Okay, look, I know what a good person you are,
可有時別人會覺得你表現得有點毒舌
but sometimes people think you might come off a little harsh.
什么
What?
我是我這輩子認識最甜的人了
I'm, like, the sweetest person I know.
甜得像樹里做小餅干的童話人物
Look at me. I should be in a tree baking cookies.
可是有些時候
Yes, but once in a while,
有人會覺得你有點刻薄
people think you're a little mean.
是嗎
Oh, yeah?
你是那些人中的一員嗎
You one of those people?
不  不是不是
No. No, no, no.
我也覺得你是做餅干那種
I-I think the cookie thing.
開始
Action.
歡迎回來
Welcome back.
今日的來賓曾來過  并廣受觀眾喜歡
Our guest today is a returning fan favorite.
兒童閱讀節目《閱讀彩虹》的主持人
He puts the reading in your rainbow,
《星際迷航:下一代》成員
the Geordi in your La Forge,
電視迷你劇集《根》的主角
and the Kunta in your Kinte,
萊瓦爾·伯頓先生
Mr. LeVar Burton.
謝謝  謝爾頓  別忘了我們的約定
Thank you, Sheldon. Now, remember our deal...
你來上節目  我刪了你的聯系方式
You do this, I delete your contact information.
而且...
While...
而且是在你面前刪
While you watch me do it.
很好  很高興再來上節目
Great. Happy to be back.
既然你來了
Well, since you're here,
我想問你對某件事的看法
I'd like to get your opinion on something.
為了向黑人歷史月致意
In honor of Black History Month,
贊頌黑人克服種種困難  以及對美國歷史的貢獻
我扮成了喬治·華盛頓·卡弗
I portrayed George Washington Carver
是美國教育家  農業化學家  植物學家
對美國有十分大貢獻的一名黑人
我對他的致敬被我室友說"超有種族歧視"
in a loving tribute that my roommate called "wildly racist"
你覺得呢
What do you think?
你好  我的名字叫喬治
Hi. My name is George.
我去  不是吧
Oh, hell, no!
聽到了嗎  萊納德
You heard him, Leonard.
"不是"吧  我沒有種族歧視
No, it's not racist.
咱們確定是這里嗎
Are we sure this is the place?
看門的說就是這棟樓
The doorman said this is the right building.
看到人來就趕緊提褲子的
I think if you're pulling up your pants,
不會是看門的  是野戰的
you're not a doorman.
誰啊
Who is it?
我想找夏普教授
Uh, I'm looking for a Professor Sharpe?
等等
Hold on.
-有事嗎  -您好  我們是大學的人
- Can I help you? - Hi. We're from the university.
我們想從您這打聽艾伯特教授的信息
We're trying to get some information about Professor Abbott.
我們在清理他的辦公室時
We were cleaning out his office
發現了一些寫滿數字的本子
and found these books full of numbers.
您知道這是什么嗎
Any chance you know what it is?
知道  他總是在搞這玩意
Yes, he was always working on this.
我猜可能是某種星際坐標系
I was thinking it might be some sort of interstellar coordinate system,
或許是哈勃定律的升級版
maybe an updated version of Hubble's law.
哈勃定律通常被用來推算遙遠星系的距離
"90"這個數字總是重復出現
I keep seeing the number 90 repeating.
那可能是某個遙遠星系的攝動角度
That could be the angle of perturbation of a distant galaxy.
其實是一份酸奶的卡路里數
It's the number of calories in a yogurt.
這是他的飲食日記
That's his food diary.
真的假的
Really?
真的  他吃什么都要記下來
Yeah, he wrote down everything he ever ate.
他堅信限制卡路里攝入量
He was convinced that calorie restriction
是長命百歲的關鍵
was the key to living forever.
那管用嗎
Does it work?
你鬧呢
Seriously?
他可能是死于車禍啊  你又不知道
Well, he could have been hit by a bus. You don't know.
抱歉  真相不是那么有趣
Sorry it's not more interesting.
往好的方面想  你們不必聽
On the bright side, you didn't have to listen
他35年來肚子餓得咕嚕叫的聲音
to his stomach growl for 35 years.
那艾伯特教授這輩子研究的東西
So, was there anything that Professor Abbott worked on
難道沒有半點算得上是成就的東西嗎
during his life that came close to an accomplishment?
老實說  他的研究一無所成
To be honest, his research never amounted to anything.
你是他的同事
Oh. You were his colleague.
你的研究結果如何
How did your research turn out?
很棒
Great.
得諾貝爾獎的人  都住這種"豪宅"
Hey, this is the apartment you get when you win a Nobel.
你可以是一個很簡樸的人啊
Well, you could be very frugal.
我真是受夠了每個人都在說反話了
I'm getting a little tired of everybody's sarcasm.
我不是惡霸
I'm not a bully.
或許我是表現得有那么一點強勢
I mean, maybe I come off a little strong,
但那只是因為我父親從小教育我要強硬
but that's only because my dad raised me to be tough
不要隨便受人欺負
and not to take crap from anybody.
那當然可以啊
No. That's fine,
但強硬跟告訴你的朋友
but there's a difference between being tough
她的新褲子像一塊松垮的尿布
and telling your friend her new pants
這兩者還是有區別的
look like a saggy diaper.
我的確那么說了  是吧
I did say that, didn't I?
是的  你說了
Yeah, you did.
我當時超級難為情  我只好把褲子退了
I felt so self-conscious, I had to return them.
退到哪兒  嬰兒用品店嗎
Where? To Babies R Us?
你又來了
You're doing it again!
對不起  我們可以走了嗎
Okay, sorry. Can we just go?
我感覺大家都討厭我
I feel like everybody hates me.
別這樣  他們不討厭你  好嗎
Oh, come on, they don't hate you, all right?
他們只是有點怕你而已
They're just a little intimidated.
你只需讓大家看到
All you need to do is show everyone
你其實非常親切
how sweet you really are.
-我還是走吧  -不  坐下
- I think I'd rather go. - No, come on.
你哪兒也不許去  知道嗎
You are not going anywhere, all right?
我在這陪著你  我們一起來解決這問題
I am here for you, and we are gonna fix this together.
謝謝
Thank you.
雖然你今天的裙子很難看
Even though your dress is ugly.
我的小旗友們
Well, my little Flag-keteers,
最后一集《有趣的旗幟》就要結束了
it looks like the last episode of Fun with Flags is at an end.
如果可以
If I could,
你們每個人都是我升上去后
I would run each and every one of you viewers up a flagpole
原俗語直翻為"升到旗桿上  看看有沒有人會敬禮"
意思是試試水  看看反應的意思
愿意敬禮的旗幟
and salute you.
如果你掉到地面  我會燒掉你
And if you touched the ground, burn you.
根據規定  美國國旗降旗時  不能觸碰地面
如果國旗被弄臟或要退役  得莊重處理  通常燒毀
我想花一點時間
I'd like to take a moment
親自謝謝艾米·費拉·福勒博士
to personally thank Dr. Amy Farrah Fowler,
你們或許知道  也或許不知道
who you may or may not know
她是第一位搭檔主持關于旗幟
is the first woman to co-host a flag
或橫幅相關的網絡寓教于樂節目的女性
or banner-related Internet info-tainment show.
聽見了嗎  玻璃天花板
Take that, glass ceiling.
玻璃天花板是指女性和少數族裔無法晉升到決策層的無形障礙
請容許我認真地說幾句
And if I may get serious for a moment,
主持這檔節目
hosting this show has been...
是一段瘋狂的旅程
one crazy ride.
一路走來的高興與失落
With all its ups and downs,
是我無論如何都不想放棄的
I wouldn't give it up for the world.
除了現在  我要放棄這節目了
Except for now, when I'm giving it up.
在節目正式停播前  我想...
Before I sign off, I'd, uh...
我想跟大家分享白旗的最后一個用處
I'd like to share with you all one last use for a white flag.
像這種時候  可以拿來擦眼淚
It's good for times like this.
晚安
Good night.
停
Cut.
謝爾頓
Sheldon...
剛才那段話太感人了
that was beautiful.
如果你沒有按下錄制...
If you didn't press record...
老娘按了
I pressed it!
結束了
Well, that's it.
羅杰·艾伯特的東西清理完畢
That's the end of Roger Abbott.
我們仍不知道是誰陷害了他
And we still don't know who framed him.
兔子羅杰的電影名為《誰陷害了兔子羅杰》
我一直在思考  一個人的一生
I still keep thinking about how an entire life
怎么能一無所成呢
can seemingly amount to nothing.
事實就是這么悲哀
I guess the sad truth is,
不是所有人都能功成名就
not everyone will accomplish something great.
我們中有些人注定要在
Some of us may just have to find meaning
日常生活的點滴中尋找生命的意義
in the little moments that make up life.
這個看待的方法很不錯
That's a nice way of looking at it.
對你而言是  我可不是
Yeah for you, not for me.
哥上過太空呢  此生足矣
I went to space. I'm covered.
不如這樣
You know what?
這瓶香檳本來就是要慶祝成就的
This bottle was meant to celebrate an achievement.
我們做個約定
Let's make a pact.
當我們中有人獲得人生中第一次重大突破時
When one of us gets their first big breakthrough,
我們就打開這瓶香檳慶祝
we'll celebrate by opening this bottle of champagne
并向羅杰·艾伯特致敬
and toasting Professor Abbott.
我喜歡這主意
I love that.
我也是
Yeah, me, too.
當然還包括
Then, of course,
向謝爾頓炫耀我們的成果
rubbing our success in Sheldon's face.
-這是最精彩的部分  -沒錯
- Oh, well, that's the best part. - Oh, yeah.
丹  我能和你聊聊嗎
Dan, could I talk to you for a minute?
好的  說吧
Sure, go ahead.
我只是想告訴你
Just want you to know I didn't mean
我不是故意侮辱你的孫子
to be rude about your grandson.
沒關系
No, it's okay.
不  有關系
No, it's not.
佩妮告訴我  大家都怕我
Penny told me that everyone's scared of me.
怎么會  怎么會
What? What?
她為什么那么說
Why would she say that?
-你知道她是酒鬼  會亂說話吧  -少來
- You know she drinks, right? - What?
不  她說得對  我要讓你知道
No, she's right, and I just want you to know
從現在起  我會多體會大家心情
that from now on, I'm gonna be much more sensitive.
我不想讓大家在我面前如履薄冰
I don't want anyone walking on eggshells around me.
那好吧  有件事
Oh, well, okay, then, uh,
我一直想告訴你
one thing I've been meaning to tell you
公司不再給我們提供免費的咖啡了
is that the company is gonna stop paying for our coffee.
沒問題  什么時候開始
No problem. When does that start?
五個月前
Five months ago.
-什么  -沒錯
- What?! - Yeah.
那我的咖啡一直都是誰買的
Who's been paying for my coffee?
我們大伙兒
All of us.
買咖啡的錢來自你一罵人
Yeah. It comes from the swear jar
我們就投錢進去的那個臟話罐
we put money in when you curse.
還有什么事是我不知道的
What else don't I know about?
-你的私人衛生間  -怎么了
- Uh, well, you know your private bathroom? - Yeah?
那應該是給整層樓的人使用的
That was supposed to be for the whole floor.
-你開什么玩笑  -那個無所謂
- You're kidding. - No, no. It's okay.
其實只對輪椅妹凱西有影響
It only really affected wheelchair Kathy,
現在她已經回醫院了
and she's back in the hospital now,
所以沒什么問題了
so it all worked out.
我感覺好難過哦
I feel so bad.
那你就不應該給人家取名"輪椅妹凱西"啊
Well, then, maybe you shouldn't have named her "Wheelchair Kathy."
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
我以為大家都喜歡我  其實我只是個怪獸
I thought everybody liked me, but I'm just a monster.
但很可愛呀  就像《怪獸公司》里的獨眼怪
But a cute one, like that, uh, eyeball guy in Monsters, Inc.
不  我最壞了
No, I'm the worst.
我是個壞人
I'm a terrible person.
乖  別哭  沒關系啦
Come on, don't cry. It's okay.
有關系
It's not okay.
我哪還有臉留在這工作呀
How can I even work here anymore? Oh.
-這家公司需要你  -真沒事
- Because this company needs you. - It's fine.
我們不介意給你買咖啡
We don't mind paying for the coffee.
我不能讓你們這么做
I can't let you do that.
或許我們可以給你
Maybe we could get you
買一臺咖啡機放在你辦公室里
an espresso machine for your office.
-這樣也行吧  -好的
- I guess that would be all right. - All right.
瞧  你不刻薄也能得到你想要的東西
See? You don't have to be mean to get what you want.
此話有理
You're right.
那我的私人衛生間現在怎么處理呢
Now where did we land on my bathroom?
好啊
Hi.
回來啦
Hello.
這么晚還不睡嗎
How come you're up so late?
我上傳《有趣的旗幟》最終集好幾個小時了
I posted the last episode of Fun with Flags hours ago,
沒有任何人在乎到愿意留個言
and not a single person cared enough to comment.
一切努力都是徒然
All that effort for nothing.
我明白你的感受
I know how you feel.
我今天一天把一個男人一生事業扔進垃圾桶
I spent the day throwing out a man's entire career,
唯一留下的是一瓶陳年香檳
and all that's left is an old bottle of champagne
和拉杰自以為沒人發現
and a naked lady pen that Raj took
就私吞了的一根裸女筆
when he thought no one was looking.
這根本是兩碼事
It's not the same thing.
你完全不明白我的感受
I don't think you know how I feel at all.
是難過嗎
Sad?
看來你真的懂我
You do get me.
有人留言了
Someone left a comment.
他們說什么
Yeah. What did they say?
"你的節目結束了真可惜
"Too bad your show is done.
我還挺喜歡的"
I kind of liked it."
萊納德  你聽到了嗎
Leonard, did you hear that?
網友們難過得要死
Oh, the people are heartbroken!
這世界上不能沒有這節目
I can't take this away from the world!
《有趣的旗幟》滿血復活了
Fun with Flags is back!
恭喜
Congratulations.
我們來慶祝吧
Let's celebrate!
謝爾頓  那不是給你的
Sheldon, that wasn't for you!
我也沒打算喝啊
Oh, no, I'm not going to drink it.
我只想聽開瓶那砰的一聲
I just wanted to hear the pop.
我知道會砰的一聲  還是嚇死人家了
Yeah, I knew it was coming. Still scary.
萊瓦爾·伯頓
LeVar Burton?
LeVar Burton!
萊瓦爾·伯頓
你來干嘛
What are you doing here?
你不讓我打電話給你
You told me not to call,
我不知道該怎么告訴你這個好消息
and I didn't know how else to give you the good news.
《有趣的旗幟》回歸了
Fun with Flags is back,
下一集你可以來當嘉賓
and you can be in the next episode.
威爾·惠頓讓我弄個大閘門
Wil Wheaton said, get a gate.
-我當初真該聽他的話  -你真是...
- I don't know why I didn't get a gate. - You...
至少你聽我說完前提
At least listen to the premise.
既然你在德國出生
Since you were born in Germany,
我們可以聊聊德國國旗
I thought we could talk about German flags.
你有興趣裝扮成卐字圖案嗎
How do you feel about dressing up like a swastika?
德國納粹旗  該卐與佛教的卍相反